Where do you come from?
你来自哪里?
I come from Greece.
我来自Greece.
What's the climate like in your country?
你们的国家的气候怎么样?
It's very pleasant.
气候非常宜人.
What's the weather like in spring?
春季的天气怎么样?
It's often windy in March.
3月里常常刮风.
It's always warm in April and May,
4月和5月的天气总是暖洋洋的,
but it rains sometimes.
但有时下雨.
What's it like in summer?
夏季的天气如何呢?
The sun shines every day.
每天都出太阳.
Is it cold or warm in autumn?
秋季的天气是冷还是暖呢?
It's always warm in September and October.
9月和10月总是很暖和.
It's often cold in November and it rains sometimes.
11月常常就冷了, 而且有时下雨.
Is it very cold in winter?
冬季的天气很冷吗?
It's often cold in December, January and February.
12月, 1月和2月常常很冷，
It snows sometimes.
有时还下雪.